BEATRIZ STROBEL

Grand Rapids, MI

Phone: (616) 228-5154 | Email: beatrizstrobel@proton.me LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/beatriz-strobel-50a58a27b

GitHub: https://github.com/beastrobel

Portfolio: https://beatriz-strobel-portfolio.onrender.com

SUMMARY

Lead UX Designer with just under 10 years of experience in Graphic Design, and a Web Development Certificate from Michigan State University. Strong ability to design, prototype, and develop web applications. Effective at Agile and working in teams in a fast-paced environment. Strong communication skills and project management skills. Passionate about continuous learning. Attentive to detail, proactive, and creative problem-solver.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technical Languages: React.js, Apollo GraphQL, Express.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js,

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ¡Query

Applications: Figma, Adobe Creative Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects,

Acrobat, and Microsoft 365

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

FAITH Catholic Lead UX Designer (Magazine Archive Lead)

Lansing, MI

2023-Current

Assumed the role of Lead UX Designer for FAITH Catholic's digital magazine archive. Oversees features, functionality, and continuous improvement of the web application. Conducts user research, writes user stories and surveys. Designs wireframes and prototypes for the web application on Figma. Conducts usability and accessibility testing and follows WCAG standards.

Graphic Designer 2021– Current

Designs high-quality print magazines in a fast-paced environment. Manages multiple client accounts. Creates digital editions and web images. Key Accomplishments:

- 2023 Catholic Media Association Award: 2nd place for Best Special Issue, "The Catholic Miscellany", June 2022.
- 2022 Catholic Media Association Award: 3rd place for Best Spanish Cover, "The Catholic Miscellany", October 2021.

Right to Life of Michigan Graphic Designer

Grand Rapids, MI

2016-2021

Designed social media graphics, flyers, logos, and benefit dinner invitation packages. Designed and developed a responsive website (self-taught at the time) using HTML, CSS, and Google Maps API. Collaborated on-site with a professional photographer and local charities in Detroit to create content for helpinthed.org.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate: Michigan State University, Lansing, MI Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design: University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI